(light music in background)
(people chattering)
("Smooth")
♪ Man, it's a hot one ♪
♪ Like seven inches from the midday sun ♪
♪ Well, I hear you whisper
and the words melt everyone ♪
♪ But you stay so cool ♪
♪ My munequita, my
Spanish Harlem Mona Lisa ♪
♪ You're my reason for reason ♪
♪ The step in my groove ♪
♪ And if you said this
life ain't good enough ♪
♪ I would give my world to lift you up ♪
♪ I could change my life
to better suit your mood ♪
♪ Because you're so smooth ♪
♪ And it's just like the
ocean under the moon ♪
♪ Oh, it's the same as the
emotion that I get from you ♪
♪ You got the kind of lovin'
that can be so smooth, yeah ♪
♪ Give me your heart, make it
real, or else forget about it ♪
♪ But I'll tell you one thing ♪
♪ If you would leave
it'd be a crying shame ♪
♪ In every breath and every word ♪
♪ I hear your name calling me out ♪
♪ Out from the barrio ♪
♪ You hear my rhythm on your radio ♪
♪ You feel the turning of
the world, so soft and slow ♪
♪ It's turning you round and round ♪
♪ And if you said this
life ain't good enough ♪
♪ I would give my world to lift you up ♪
♪ I could change my life
to better suit your mood ♪
♪ Because you're so smooth ♪
♪ Well, and it's just like
the ocean under the moon ♪
♪ Well, it's the same as the
emotion that I get from you ♪
♪ You got the kind of lovin'
that can be so smooth, yeah ♪
♪ Give me your heart, make it
real, or else forget about it ♪
♪ And it's just like the
ocean under the moon ♪
♪ It's the same as the
emotion that I get from you ♪
♪ You got the kind of lovin'
that can be so smooth, yeah ♪
♪ Give me your heart, make it
real, or else forget about it ♪
♪ Or else forget about it ♪
♪ Oh, let's don't forget about it ♪
♪ Give me your heart, make it real ♪
♪ Let's don't forget about it, hey ♪
♪ Let's don't forget about
it, now, oh, now, oh ♪
it, now, now, now, oh ♪
♪ Let's don't forget about
it, hey, now, now, oh ♪
♪ Let's don't forget
about it, hey, hey, hey ♪